Rafael Wiska-Ilnicki

Email: rafwiskailnicki@gmail.com

Website: rafaelwi.github.io

PROFILE

Second-year University of Guelph Software Engineering student attaining a Bachelor of Computing with Business Minor. Summer Research assistant for the School of Computer Science performing data cleaning, sorting, and integration. Teaching assistant for a first-year Computer Science course aiding in planning, marking, and invigilation. Experience in Python, C, and Java.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Teaching Assistant (CIS*1250 Software Design I) | September 2019 – December 2019 School of Computer Science, University of Guelph | Guelph, ON

- Collaborated with a team of four to plan, schedule, and organize labs and tests
- Marked and provided valuable feedback to students on tests and exams
- Invigilated quizzes, tests, and exams

Undergraduate Research Assistant | May 2019 – August 2019

School of Computer Science, University of Guelph | Guelph, ON

- Developed a criminal offence categorization engine from scratch using Python
- Applied manual and automated data cleaning techniques to a database of historical records
- Utilized fuzzy matching and other data matching principles to sort and link historical records

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computing, Software Engineering (Co-op) | September 2018 – Present University of Guelph | Guelph, ON

- Pursuing a minor in Business
- Dean's List 3.7 GPA cumulative

Key Academic Projects

Dungeons and Dragons Level Generator (CIS*2430 Object-Oriented Programming, Fall 2019)

- Developed a tool in Java to help Dungeon Masters create levels for *Dungeons and Dragons*
- Used JavaFX to implement a GUI for ease of use

Great Canadian Consumer Price Index Report (CIS*2550 Software Design II, Winter 2019)

- Worked in a team of four to develop a program to analyze consumer price index data
- Integrated R to generate scatterplots and bar graphs

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, Java, C, Go, HTML/CSS, JavaScript **Collaboration Tools:** GitHub, GitLab, Slack, Trello **Project Management:** Agile, Kanban, Waterfall

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Discord Bot: Designed to highlight user's most memorable messages. Built using Go.

Personal Website: Built using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and Jekyll.